adpackpro-international.com 2017-06-06

# 

**1\. For which offer is this privacy statement valid?**   
This privacy statement is valid for every website of the Onevision Holding AG (e.g. www.jopsolutions.com) and all products of the Onevision Holding AG (e.g. jopbooster). Should you decide to use a service of the Onevision Holding AG in return for remuneration, payment will be done through a third party (digistore24). In this case this privacy statement will not apply for a third party. Moreover our side contains links to external web pages of third parties. This privacy statement will not apply for those webpages. 

**2\. Which data will be recored and how will it be used?**   
In this privacy statement we indicate information about the collection and use of personal data, data about payment methods, gaming data and usage data. 

**2.1 personal data**   
Personal data are individual claims about personal or factual circumstances about your person. If you enjoy a service or product of the Onevision AG for a fee or free of charge, you will possibly receive member access. For this purpose indicate your e-mail address and if appropriate a self chosen user name (pseudonym). Your password will be secured encrypted. 

**2.2 Data about payment methods**   
Data about payment methods are necessary, to handle purchase of services or products for a fee. We are legally obliged to keep and store documents of purchases for ten years. 

**2.3 User Data**   
User Data are data, which accrue while using the website. This can be for example the number of page views or the used browser. Every log-in will save your ip-address* and type of browser as well as time of log-in. This is necessary for the use of our member area, as only in this way fraud and abuse can be prevented. 

**3 To whom the data become passed on?**   
If you use services for a fee, we will collect and save your order data (name, address, email address). This is necessary for service delivery. 

**3.1 Email-Marketing Providers**   
We have concluded a contract for data processing with our Email Marketing provider „klick-tipp“. This ensures that our provider at all points will keep to the strict regulations of the swiss data protection. This also ensures that your data will only be stored and safed within the E.U. with high level of protection. A storage of your data on servers outside of the E.U. will not happen. 

**4\. Information about cookies**   
So-called cookies will be used to recognize repeated use of a service by the same user. Cookies are small text files, which your internet browser drops and saves on your computer. If you call up our site again those cookies will emit information to recognize you. This recognition is based on the information saved in the cookies. The information thus obtained is used to optimize our services and products and to grant you an easier access. You can prevent saving of cookies on your hard disk by choosing „block all cookies“ in your browser settings. Please note that this can lead to a functional limitation of our services. 

**5\. Data Protection in relation to children**   
Onevision Holding AG also wants to protect privacy of children. That is why we ask parents and legal guardians to give active support to children while using the internet. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under 13 years. Our offer does not concern children 13 years. 

**6\. Modification of this Declaration**   
Under certain Circumstances it can happen that the data conditions or regulations will be changed. In this situation we will change this declaration and the time stamp below. Moreover we will call your attention to it in the member area. 

**7\. Information**   
In order to obtain information about stored personal data please choose the menu item „account“ in the main menu within the member area. Moreover you can send an inquiry by using the contact form. More contact options can be found in the imprint. *A IP-adress marks a computer, cell phone or different device with a TCP/IP network. TCP/IP stands for Transmission Control Protocol/ Internet Protocol. The internet is a network which uses this protocol. The data exchange with your computer / cell phone is only made possible through the IP-address, so that you can use online offers such as our member area in the internet. 

**Data Protection**   
In General the use of our website is normally possible without without providing any personal data. Insofar as personal data is prohibited on our sites (e.g. name, address or email address), if possible, it will always happen on volunteer basis. This data will not be processed to third parties without your explicit consent.   
Please note that the transfer of data in the internet (e.g. communication via email) may have security vulnerarbility. Complete Protection to the unauthorised access of your data by third parties is not possible.   
The utilization of contact data published within the bounds of the imprint obligation by a third party for the consignment of advertisments and information which was not specifically ordered, is herewith explicitly objected to.   
The operators of this website shall retain the right to undertake legal steps if we are send unsolicited advertisements, for example, in the form of spam mails. 

**Data Protection Declaration for use of facebook plugins (like-button)**   
Our Websites use plug-ins for the social networking site Facebook (Facebook Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, California, 94025 USA). You will recognize the Facebook Plugins from the Facebook logo or the like button. („I Like“) on our website.   
Here you will find an overwiew of facebook plug-ins: http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/. If you visit our site, the plug-in will automatically establish a direct connection between your browser and the facebook server. Thus Facebook will receive the information, that you visited our Website with your IP-address. If you press the „like-button“ while your logged in to your facebook account you can link contents of our site to your facebook profile. In this way Facebook can assign the visit on our websites to your user account. Please note that we, as a provider of these websites, have no knowledge of content of the reported data as well as its use by Facebook. More information on this can be found in the imprint of facebook under http://de-de.facebook.com/policy.php. If you do not want Facebook to assign your visit on our sites to your facebook account, please log out from your facebook account. 

**Data Privacy Statement for the use of Google Analytics**   
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. („Google“). Google Analytics uses so-called „Cookies“, text files, which will be stored and saved on your computer and enable an analysis of your use of the website. The information, created by the cookie by using this website, will normally be send and saved to a server of Google in the USA. In case of activation of IP anonymisation on this website, your IP address will be shortened before, within Member States of the European Union or in other Contracting States being part of the Agreement on the European Economic by Google. Only in exceptional cases the whole IP address will be sent to a server of Google in the USA and shortened there. Under the Authority of the provider of this website. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to produce reports on website activities for their operators and to provide other services related to the use of the website and of the internet.   
The IP address sent to your browser in the context of Google Analytics will not be joined with outher data of Google. You can prevent storage of cookies by appropriate settings in your browser software; we would like to make you aware of the fact that in this case you consequently cannot use all functions of this website to the full extend.   
Furthermore you have the possibility to prevent registration of use of this website related data (developed through cookies) by Google, as well as processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the relevant browser plugin on the following link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de. 

**Data privacy Statement for the use of Google+1**   
Collection and Dissemination of information:   
With the help of the "Google+1" button you can share information worldwide. Via the Google+1 button you and other members will receive customized contents of Google and our partners. Google stores and saves information for which you pressed the +1 Icon as well as the information about the site you were watching while pressing the +1 icon. Your +1 can be displayed as references along with your profile image in search results, other google profiles or other sites and displays in the internet. Google records information about your +1 activities, to improve Google Services for you and other members. To use the Google+1 button you have to own a public profile which can be seen around the world and has to contain the name you chose for the profile. This name will be used on all Google Services. In some cases this name can replace another name, which you used by sharing of content via your Google account. The identity of your Google Profile can be shown to users who know your email address or other identifying information about you. 

**Use of collected information:**   
Besides the above mentioned purposes your provided information will be used according to the applicable privacy laws of Google. Google possibly publishes summarised statistics about the +1 activities of users resp. forwards them to users and partners, as for example publishers, advertisers or connected websites. 

**Datenschutzerklärung für die Nutzung von Twitter**  
Functions such as Twitter are integrated on our websites. This functions will be offered by Twitter Inc., Twitter Inc. 1355 market St., Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA. By using Twitter and the function „retweed“ your visited websites will be connected to your twitter account and will be shown to other users. Thereby data will also be transmitted to twitter. Please note that we, as provider of these websites, do not receive any information of the contents transmitted as well as its using by Twitter. Further information about it can be found in the privacy policy of twitter under: http://twitter.com/privacy. Your privacy settings on Twitter can be changed in your account settings under http://twitter.com/account/settings. Information, Deletion, Blocking 

You have the right to free information about your stored personal data, their origin and recipient as well as a right of adjustment, blocking or deletion of this data, at any time. For this as well as other questions about personal data you can contact us via the address in the imprint of the website provider at any time.
